<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NASA</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="welcome">Image of the Day</string>
    <string name="about_title">About NASA</string>
    <string name="about">The National Aeronautics and Space Administration is America’s civil space program and the global leader in space exploration. The agency has a diverse workforce of just under 18,000 civil servants, and works with many more U.S. contractors, academia, and international and commercial partners to explore, discover, and expand knowledge for the benefit of humanity. With an annual budget of $23.2 billion in Fiscal Year 2021, which is less than 0.5% of the overall U.S. federal budget, NASA supports more than 312,000 jobs across the United States, generating more than $64.3 billion in total economic output (Fiscal Year 2019).

At its 20 centers and facilities across the country – and the only National Laboratory in space – NASA studies Earth, including its climate, our Sun, and our solar system and beyond. We conduct research, testing, and development to advance aeronautics, including electric propulsion and supersonic flight. We develop and fund space technologies that will enable future exploration and benefit life on Earth.

NASA also leads a Moon to Mars exploration approach, which includes working with U.S. industry, international partners, and academia to develop new technology, and send science research and soon humans to explore the Moon on Artemis missions that will help prepare for human exploration of the Red Planet. In addition to those major missions, the agency shares what it learns so that its information can make life better for people worldwide. For example, companies use NASA discoveries and technologies to create new products for the public. To ensure future success for the agency and the nation, NASA also supports education efforts in STEM with an emphasis on increasing diversity in our future workforce.</string>
    <string name="images_title">NASA Images</string>
    <string name="images_description">Please select a date using the button below to see a picture.</string>
    <string name="date_picker">Date</string>
    <string name="saveBtn">SAVE PICTURE</string>
    <string name="deleteBtn">DELETE PICTURE</string>
    <string name="images_downloaded_title">Downloaded Files</string>
    <string name="addBtn">ADD NAME</string>
    <string name="emptylist">Folder empty. Please go to the Images page to save NASA pictures.</string>
    <string name="homepageText">Discover the cosmos! Each day a different image or photograph of our fascinating universe is featured, along with a brief explanation written by a professional.</string>
    <string name="downloadNASAImages">Downloaded NASA images..</string>
    <string name="HELP">HELP is coming...</string>
    <string name="HELPTITLE">HELP</string>
    <string name="help_about">This is the ABOUT NASA page. To download an image, please select the NASA icon and then Images.</string>
    <string name="home_toast">Home</string>
    <string name="about_nasa_toast">About NASA</string>
    <string name="images_toast">Images</string>
    <string name="exit_toast">Goodbye</string>
    <string name="help_download">In order to select a picture, please click the date button and click the desired date. The picture and it/s details will populate. If you/d like to save a copy of this picture, please select the Save Picture button. To view saved pictures, click the downloaded folder in the top right next to the HELP icon.</string>
    <string name="download_saved_end">/ has been saved.</string>
    <string name="picture_title">Picture: /</string>
    <string name="prev_download_end">/ was previously saved.</string>
    <string name="help_imagelist">The list below are the downloaded pictures. Click a picture to view! A prompt will ask if you/d like to delete a picture.</string>
    <string name="delete">DELETE</string>
    <string name="delete_success">/ has been deleted.</string>
    <string name="delete_failed">/ is unable to be deleted.</string>
    <string name="CANCEL">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="help_home">Please add your name to get started. Select the NASA icon to get the menu.</string>
</resources>